<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Product xmlns='http://code.google.com/p/open-zwave/'>
	<CommandClass id="112" name="COMMAND_CLASS_CONFIGURATION" version="1" request_flags="4"  >
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="1" label="Device Type">
			<Help>
				This parameter is read only and indicates in which mode the device is included. 
				The device can be included either in the Binary Switch mode or in the Thermostat mode.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="list" genre="config" index="2" label="Frequency Region" min="0" max="9" value="0"> 
			<Help>
				The HLS01 has Z-Wave 700 platform chip inside which allows to use the device in different Z-Wave frequencies. 
				If there is a need to use the device in the frequency different from the factory default change the value of 
				this parameter according to the frequency list.
			</Help>
			<Item label="EU (868.4 MHz, 869.85 MHz)" value="0" />
			<Item label="US (908.4 MHz, 916.0 MHz)" value="1" />
			<Item label="ANZ (919.8 MHz, 921.4 MHz)" value="2" />
			<Item label="HK (919.8 MHz)" value="3" />
			<Item label="IN (865.2 MHz)" value="4" />
			<Item label="IL (916.0 MHz)" value="5" />
			<Item label="RU (869.0 MHz)" value="6" />
			<Item label="CH (868.4 MHz)" value="7" />
			<Item label="JP (922.5 MHz, 923.9 MHz, 926.3 MHz)" value="8" />
			<Item label="KR (920.9 MHz, 921.7 MHz, 923.1 MHz)" value="9" />
		</Value>
		<Value type="list" genre="config" index="3" label="Output NO/NC Mode" value="0">
			<Help>
				The device can operate in Normal Open (NO) mode and in Normal Close (NC) mode. If the Parameter value = 0, 
				the device switch operates in NO mode and there is no voltage on output when the device is in OFF state. 
				The output will be powered when device goes to ON state. If the Parameter value = 1, the output will be 
				powered in OFF state and will be no voltage on output when the device is in ON state.
				The factory default value is 0.
			</Help>
			<Item label="Normal Open (NO) mode" value="0" />
			<Item label="Normal Close (NC) mode" value="1" />
		</Value>
		<Value type="list" genre="config" index="4" label="Time Correction by Gateway" value="1">
			<Help>
				If this Parameter value = 1 and the HE-HLS01 is connected to a Z-Wave gateway, the HE-HLS01 time and day will be periodically polled
				and corrected from the gateway. To switch off auto-correction set the Parameter value to 0. The factory default value is 1.
			</Help>
			<Item label="Time auto-correction disabled" value="0" />
			<Item label="Time auto-correction enabled" value="1" />
		</Value>
		<Value type="list" genre="config" index="5" label="Day of the Week" value="1">
			<Help>
				This Parameter allows manual adjustment of the day of the week in case the HE-HLS01 is not connected to any Z-Wave gateway
				or auto-correction is disabled (Parameter 4 value is 0). The factory default value is 1.
			</Help>
			<Item label="Monday" value="1" />
			<Item label="Tuesday" value="2" />
			<Item label="Wednesday" value="3" />
			<Item label="Thursday" value="4" />
			<Item label="Friday" value="5" />
			<Item label="Saturday" value="6" />
			<Item label="Sunday" value="7" />
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="6" label="Clock Hours" min="0" max="23" value="0">
			<Help>
				Allows manually adjustment of hours for internal clock in case the HE-HLS01 is not connected to any Z-Wave gateway or 
				the Parameter 04 (auto-correction) is set to 0. The value of this parameter can be set from 0 to 23.
				The factory default value is 0.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="7" label="Clock Minutes" min="0" max="59" value="0">
			<Help>
				Allows manually adjustment of minutes for internal clock in case the HE-HLS01 is not connected to any Z-Wave gateway or 
				the Parameter 04 (auto-correction) is set to 0. The value of this parameter can be set from 0 to 59. 
				The factory default value is 0.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="8" label="External NTC Temperature Sensor Resistance" min="1" max="100" value="10">
			<Help>
				If the external NTC temperature sensor is used it is necessary to select the correct resistance value in Ohms (Ω) of 
				the sensor. The selection range is 1 to 100 kiloOhms (kΩ). One 10kΩ NTC temperature sensor is included in the HE-HLS01 
				package with a 3-meter connection wire. The factory default value is 10.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		//Valeurs négatives ??
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="9" label="Temperature Sensor Calibration" min="-100" max="100" value="0">
			<Help>
				This Parameter defines the offset value for external NTC temperature sensor. If the temperature sensor is not calibrated 
				properly, manual calibration can be made by adjusting the values up to ±10.0°C or ±18°F. This value will be added or 
				subtracted from the temperature sensor reading. The factory default value is 0.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="list" genre="config" index="10" label="Temperature Scale Mode" value="0">
			<Help>
				This parameter determines in which unit of measurement (degrees Celsius or Fahrenheit) the device will report the temperature, 
				and also determines the scale that will be interpreted by the configuration parameters.
				Factory default value is 0 (degrees Celsius).
			</Help>
			<Item label="Celsius" value="0" />
			<Item label="Fahrenheit" value="1" />
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="11" label="Temperature Sensor Consecutive Report Interval" min="1" max="120" value="10">
			<Help>
				This Parameter defines the interval between consecutive reports of temperature sensor reading to the gateway. The value can be 
				adjusted from 1 min to 120 min. The factory default value is 10.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="12" label="Temperature Sensor Report Threshold" min="1" max="100" value="5">
			<Help>
				This parameter determines the change in temperature level resulting in temperature sensors report being sent to the gateway.
				In Celsius scale mode the value of this parameter should be x10, e.g. for 0.4°C use value 4. From 1 (0.1°C) to 100 (10°C) can
				 be selected in Celsius scale mode and from 1 to 18 can be selected in Fahrenheit scale mode. Use the value 0 if there is a 
				 need to stop sending the reports. The factory default value is 5 (0.5°) in °C scale and 1 in °F scale.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="13" label="Energy Consumption Meter Consecutive Report Interval" min="1" max="120" value="10">
			<Help>
				This Parameter defines the interval between consecutive reports of real time and cumulative energy consumption data to the gateway. 
				The value can be adjusted from 1 min to 120 min. The factory default value is 10 min.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="14" label="Energy Consumption Meter Report Threshold" min="1" max="90" value="25">
			<Help>
				This parameter determines how much the cumulative or real time energy consumption data need to increase/reduce to be reported to 
				the gateway. The value of this parameter is in % and from 1 to 90 can be selected. Use the value 0 if there is a need to stop 
				sending the reports. The factory default value is 25.
				Note: Energy consumption meter function is available only if the device is AC powered.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="list" genre="config" index="15" label="Device Failure Notifications" value="1">
			<Help>
				If the HLS01 does not work properly it sends “System Failure” notification to the gateway with the error code. 
				The factory default value is 1 (the notification is enabled).
			</Help>
			<Item label="Disable “System Failure” notification" value="0" />
			<Item label="Enable “System Failure” notification" value="1" />
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="16" label="Temperature Rise Notification" min="0" max="120" value="50">
			<Help>
				Use this parameter if you want to know about temperature rise before it reaches the critical value, defined in the “Overheat Protection” 
				parameter. The device will send “Rapid Temperature Rise” notification to the gateway if the temperature sensor reading reaches the value 
				defined in this parameter. The value can be set from 1 to 120 in °C scale mode or from 32 to 248 in °F scale mode. To disable the 
				notification, set the value of this parameter to 0.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="17" label="Overheat Protection Notification" min="0" max="120" value="60">
			<Help>
				You can define the maximum limit of temperature, reaching which the device will automatically switch Off the load and send 
				“Overheat Detected” notification to the gateway. The value of this parameter can be set from 1 to 120 in °C scale mode or from 
				32 to 248 in °F scale mode. Use the value 0 if there is a need to disable this function.
				The factory default value is 60 in °C scale and 140 in °F scale.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="list" genre="config" index="18" label="Over-Current Protection Notification" value="1">
			<Help>
				The maximum load for the device is 16A. If the connected load current exceeds 16A the device will automatically switch Off the output 
				and send the “Over-Current Detected” notification to the gateway. To disable sending the notification, set the value of this Parameter to 0.
				The factory default value is 1 (the notification is enabled).
				Note: The protection works only if the device is AC powered.
			</Help>
			<Item label="“Over-Current Detected” notification disabled" value="0" />
			<Item label="“Over-Current Detected” notification enabled" value="1" />
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="19" label="Over-Load Protection Notification" min="0" max="4000" value="3500">
			<Help>
				You can define the maximum power in Watt for connected load. The device will automatically switch off the output and send “Over-Load Detected” 
				notification to the gateway if power consumed by the connected load exceeds this limit. The value of this parameter can be set from 100 to 4000 
				in watts. Use the value 0 if there is a need to disable this function. The factory default value is 3500W.
				Note: The protection works only if the device is AC powered.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="20" label="Over-Voltage Protection Notification" min="0" max="280" value="240">
			<Help>
			The device constantly monitors the voltage of your electricity network. You can define the maximum voltage of network exceeding which the device 
			will automatically switch off the output and send “Over-Voltage Detected” notification to the gateway. The value of this parameter can be set 
			from 120 to 280 in volts. Use the value 0 if there is a need to disable this function.
			The factory default value is 240V.
			Note: The protection works only if the device is AC powered.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="21" label="Voltage Drop Protection Notification" min="0" max="240" value="200">
			<Help>
				You can define the minimum voltage of your electricity network. If the voltage of the network drops determined level the device will automatically 
				switch off the output and send “Voltage Drop Detected” notification to the gateway. The value of this parameter can be set from 80 to 240 in volts. 
				Use the value 0 if there is a need to disable this function. The factory default value is 200V.
				Note: The protection works only if the device is AC powered.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="list" genre="config" index="22" label="Sparks Protection Notification" value="1">
			<Help>
				If connected load fails it can create sparks that may cause a fire. The device constantly monitors the power consumption of connected load and can 
				detect even a small surge in consumption and automatically switch off the output and send “Surge Detected” notification to the gateway.
				The factory default value is 1 (the protection is enabled).
				Note: The protection works only if the device is AC powered.
			</Help>
			<Item label="Disabling “Surge Detected” notification" value="0" />
			<Item label="Enabling “Surge Detected” notification" value="1" />
		</Value>
		<Value type="list" genre="config" index="31" label="Load Error Notification" value="1">
			<Help>
				The device can send the “Load Error” notification to the gateway when the relay is On but there is
				no power consumption (meaning possible problems with the heating system). 
				The factory default value is 1 (the notification is enabled).
				Note: The function works only if the device is AC powered.
			</Help>
			<Item label="Disable “Load Error” notification" value="0" />
			<Item label="Enable “Load Error” notification" value="1" />
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="32" label="Temperature Hysteresis" min="2" max="100" value="5">
			<Help>
				This Parameter defines the hysteresis value for temperature control. The HE-HLS01 will stabilize the temperature 
				with selected hysteresis. For example, if the SET POINT is set for 25°C and HYSTERESIS is set for 0.5°C the HE-HLS01 
				will change the state to IDLE when the temperature reaches 25.0°C, but it will change the state to HEATING if the 
				temperature drops lower than 24.5°C. The hysteresis can be changed from 0.2°C to 10.0°C range in Celsius mode, and 
				from 1°F to 18.0°F in Fahrenheit mode. The factory default value is 0.5°C and 1°F.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="list" genre="config" index="33" label="Basic Set Action" value="1">
			<Help>
				This Parameter defines which Operating Mode the HE-HLS01 reverts to if the Basic Set command is received.
				If the Basic Set command value is 0 (OFF state) the HE-HLS01 will go to Manual mode and switch Off the heating 
				element (IDLE mode). If the Basic Set command value is 0xFF (ON state) the HE-HLS01 will change the Mode 
				to the corresponding Parameter value. The factory default value is 1.
			</Help>
			<Item label="Heat Mode" value="1" />
			<Item label="Auto Mode" value="2" />
			<Item label="Dry Mode" value="3" />
			<Item label="Energy Saving Mode" value="4" />
			<Item label="Away Mode" value="5" />
		</Value>
		<Value type="list" genre="config" index="34" label="External Input Mode" value="0">
			<Help>
				Settings for external input. The factory default value is 0.
			</Help>
			<Item label="The input state changes will be ignored by the Thermostat logic." value="0" />
			<Item label="The external input will operate in “Toggle Switch” mode" value="1" />
			<Item label="The external input will operate in “Toggle Switch Reverse” mode" value="2" />
			<Item label="The external input will operate in “Push Button (Momentary Switch)" value="3" />
		</Value>
		<Value type="list" genre="config" index="35" label="External Input Action" value="1">
			<Help>
				This Parameter allows selection of which Operating Mode the HE-HLS01 should revert to when the external input is shorted.
				The factory default value is 1.
			</Help>
			<Item label="Heat Mode" value="1" />
			<Item label="Auto Mode" value="2" />
			<Item label="Dry Mode" value="3" />
			<Item label="Energy Saving Mode" value="4" />
			<Item label="Away Mode" value="5" />
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="36" label="Dry Mode Timeout" min="1" max="720" value="30">
			<Help>
				By choosing Dry Mode, the device will increase the temperature to the selected Set Point and keep it for the time specified 
				in this parameter. A time range of 1 to 720 minutes (12 hours) can be set. As the Dry Time passes, the Thermostat will 
				automatically change to the Mode set in the Parameter 37.
				The factory default value is 30 minutes.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="list" genre="config" index="37" label="Mode to Switch After Dry Mode Operation Complete" min="10" max="370" value="200">
			<Help>
				This Parameter indicates the mode that will be set after Dry Time.
				The factory default value is 1.
			</Help>
			<Item label="Heat Mode" value="1" />
			<Item label="Auto Mode" value="2" />
			<Item label="Dry Mode" value="3" />
			<Item label="Energy Saving Mode" value="4" />
			<Item label="Away Mode" value="5" />
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="38" label="Morning Schedule Time" min="0000" max="2359" value="0600">
			<Help>
				Use this Parameter to set the Morning time manually for the Temperature Schedule. The value of this Parameter has format HHMM,
				e.g. for 08:00 use value 0800 (time without a colon). From 00:00 to 23:59 can be selected.
				The factory default value is 0600.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="39" label="Day Schedule Time" min="0000" max="2359" value="0900">
			<Help>
				Use this Parameter to set the Day time manually for the Temperature Schedule. The value of this Parameter has format HHMM,
				e.g. for 08:00 use value 0800 (time without a colon). From 00:00 to 23:59 can be selected.
				The factory default value is 0900.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="40" label="Evening Schedule Time" min="0000" max="2359" value="1800">
			<Help>
				Use this Parameter to set the Evening time manually for the Temperature Schedule. The value of this Parameter has format HHMM,
				e.g. for 08:00 use value 0800 (time without a colon). From 00:00 to 23:59 can be selected.
				The factory default value is 1800.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="41" label="Night Schedule Time" min="0000" max="2359" value="2300">
			<Help>
				Use this Parameter to set the Night time manually for the Temperature Schedule. The value of this Parameter has format HHMM,
				e.g. for 08:00 use value 0800 (time without a colon). From 00:00 to 23:59 can be selected.
				The factory default value is 2300.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="42" label="Monday Morning temperature" min="10" max="1100" value="240">
			<Help>
				Use this Parameter to set the temperature for each day Schedule manually. The value of this Parameter should be x10,
				e.g. for 22.5°C set value 225. From 1°C (value 10) to 37°C (value 370) can be selected.
				The factory default value is 240.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="43" label="Monday Day temperature" min="10" max="1100" value="200">
			<Help>
				Use this Parameter to set the temperature for each day Schedule manually. The value of this Parameter should be x10,
				e.g. for 22.5°C set value 225. From 1°C (value 10) to 37°C (value 370) can be selected.
				The factory default value is 200.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="44" label="Monday Evening temperature" min="10" max="1100" value="230">
			<Help>
				Use this Parameter to set the temperature for each day Schedule manually. The value of this Parameter should be x10,
				e.g. for 22.5°C set value 225. From 1°C (value 10) to 37°C (value 370) can be selected.
				The factory default value is 230.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="45" label="Monday Night temperature" min="10" max="1100" value="180">
			<Help>
				Use this Parameter to set the temperature for each day Schedule manually. The value of this Parameter should be x10,
				e.g. for 22.5°C set value 225. From 1°C (value 10) to 37°C (value 370) can be selected.
				The factory default value is 180.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="46" label="Tuesday Morning temperature" min="10" max="1100" value="240">
			<Help>
				Use this Parameter to set the temperature for each day Schedule manually. The value of this Parameter should be x10,
				e.g. for 22.5°C set value 225. From 1°C (value 10) to 37°C (value 370) can be selected.
				The factory default value is 240.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="47" label="Tuesday Day temperature" min="10" max="1100" value="200">
			<Help>
				Use this Parameter to set the temperature for each day Schedule manually. The value of this Parameter should be x10,
				e.g. for 22.5°C set value 225. From 1°C (value 10) to 37°C (value 370) can be selected.
				The factory default value is 200.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="48" label="Tuesday Evening temperature" min="10" max="1100" value="230">
			<Help>
				Use this Parameter to set the temperature for each day Schedule manually. The value of this Parameter should be x10,
				e.g. for 22.5°C set value 225. From 1°C (value 10) to 37°C (value 370) can be selected.
				The factory default value is 230.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="49" label="Tuesday Night temperature" min="10" max="1100" value="180">
			<Help>
				Use this Parameter to set the temperature for each day Schedule manually. The value of this Parameter should be x10,
				e.g. for 22.5°C set value 225. From 1°C (value 10) to 37°C (value 370) can be selected.
				The factory default value is 180.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="50" label="Wednesday Morning temperature" min="10" max="1100" value="240">
			<Help>
				Use this Parameter to set the temperature for each day Schedule manually. The value of this Parameter should be x10,
				e.g. for 22.5°C set value 225. From 1°C (value 10) to 37°C (value 370) can be selected.
				The factory default value is 240.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="51" label="Wednesday Day temperature" min="10" max="1100" value="200">
			<Help>
				Use this Parameter to set the temperature for each day Schedule manually. The value of this Parameter should be x10,
				e.g. for 22.5°C set value 225. From 1°C (value 10) to 37°C (value 370) can be selected.
				The factory default value is 200.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="52" label="Wednesday Evening temperature" min="10" max="1100" value="230">
			<Help>
				Use this Parameter to set the temperature for each day Schedule manually. The value of this Parameter should be x10,
				e.g. for 22.5°C set value 225. From 1°C (value 10) to 37°C (value 370) can be selected.
				The factory default value is 230.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="53" label="Wednesday Night temperature" min="10" max="1100" value="180">
			<Help>
				Use this Parameter to set the temperature for each day Schedule manually. The value of this Parameter should be x10,
				e.g. for 22.5°C set value 225. From 1°C (value 10) to 37°C (value 370) can be selected.
				The factory default value is 180.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="54" label="Thursday Morning temperature" min="10" max="1100" value="240">
			<Help>
				Use this Parameter to set the temperature for each day Schedule manually. The value of this Parameter should be x10,
				e.g. for 22.5°C set value 225. From 1°C (value 10) to 37°C (value 370) can be selected.
				The factory default value is 240.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="55" label="Thursday Day temperature" min="10" max="1100" value="200">
			<Help>
				Use this Parameter to set the temperature for each day Schedule manually. The value of this Parameter should be x10,
				e.g. for 22.5°C set value 225. From 1°C (value 10) to 37°C (value 370) can be selected.
				The factory default value is 200.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="56" label="Thursday Evening temperature" min="10" max="1100" value="230">
			<Help>
				Use this Parameter to set the temperature for each day Schedule manually. The value of this Parameter should be x10,
				e.g. for 22.5°C set value 225. From 1°C (value 10) to 37°C (value 370) can be selected.
				The factory default value is 230.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="57" label="Thursday Night temperature" min="10" max="1100" value="180">
			<Help>
				Use this Parameter to set the temperature for each day Schedule manually. The value of this Parameter should be x10,
				e.g. for 22.5°C set value 225. From 1°C (value 10) to 37°C (value 370) can be selected.
				The factory default value is 180.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="58" label="Friday Morning temperature" min="10" max="1100" value="240">
			<Help>
				Use this Parameter to set the temperature for each day Schedule manually. The value of this Parameter should be x10,
				e.g. for 22.5°C set value 225. From 1°C (value 10) to 37°C (value 370) can be selected.
				The factory default value is 240.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="59" label="Friday Day temperature" min="10" max="1100" value="200">
			<Help>
				Use this Parameter to set the temperature for each day Schedule manually. The value of this Parameter should be x10,
				e.g. for 22.5°C set value 225. From 1°C (value 10) to 37°C (value 370) can be selected.
				The factory default value is 200.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="60" label="Friday Evening temperature" min="10" max="1100" value="230">
			<Help>
				Use this Parameter to set the temperature for each day Schedule manually. The value of this Parameter should be x10,
				e.g. for 22.5°C set value 225. From 1°C (value 10) to 37°C (value 370) can be selected.
				The factory default value is 230.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="61" label="Friday Night temperature" min="10" max="1100" value="180">
			<Help>
				Use this Parameter to set the temperature for each day Schedule manually. The value of this Parameter should be x10,
				e.g. for 22.5°C set value 225. From 1°C (value 10) to 37°C (value 370) can be selected.
				The factory default value is 180.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="62" label="Saturday Morning temperature" min="10" max="1100" value="240">
			<Help>
				Use this Parameter to set the temperature for each day Schedule manually. The value of this Parameter should be x10,
				e.g. for 22.5°C set value 225. From 1°C (value 10) to 37°C (value 370) can be selected.
				The factory default value is 240.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="63" label="Saturday Day temperature" min="10" max="1100" value="200">
			<Help>
				Use this Parameter to set the temperature for each day Schedule manually. The value of this Parameter should be x10,
				e.g. for 22.5°C set value 225. From 1°C (value 10) to 37°C (value 370) can be selected.
				The factory default value is 200.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="64" label="Saturday Evening temperature" min="10" max="1100" value="230">
			<Help>
				Use this Parameter to set the temperature for each day Schedule manually. The value of this Parameter should be x10,
				e.g. for 22.5°C set value 225. From 1°C (value 10) to 37°C (value 370) can be selected.
				The factory default value is 230.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="65" label="Saturday Night temperature" min="10" max="1100" value="180">
			<Help>
				Use this Parameter to set the temperature for each day Schedule manually. The value of this Parameter should be x10,
				e.g. for 22.5°C set value 225. From 1°C (value 10) to 37°C (value 370) can be selected.
				The factory default value is 180.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="66" label="Sunday Morning temperature" min="10" max="1100" value="240">
			<Help>
				Use this Parameter to set the temperature for each day Schedule manually. The value of this Parameter should be x10,
				e.g. for 22.5°C set value 225. From 1°C (value 10) to 37°C (value 370) can be selected.
				The factory default value is 240.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="67" label="Sunday Day temperature" min="10" max="1100" value="200">
			<Help>
				Use this Parameter to set the temperature for each day Schedule manually. The value of this Parameter should be x10,
				e.g. for 22.5°C set value 225. From 1°C (value 10) to 37°C (value 370) can be selected.
				The factory default value is 200.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="68" label="Sunday Evening temperature" min="10" max="1100" value="230">
			<Help>
				Use this Parameter to set the temperature for each day Schedule manually. The value of this Parameter should be x10,
				e.g. for 22.5°C set value 225. From 1°C (value 10) to 37°C (value 370) can be selected.
				The factory default value is 230.
			</Help>
		</Value>
		<Value type="byte" genre="config" index="69" label="Sunday Night temperature" min="10" max="1100" value="180">
			<Help>
				Use this Parameter to set the temperature for each day Schedule manually. The value of this Parameter should be x10,
				e.g. for 22.5°C set value 225. From 1°C (value 10) to 37°C (value 370) can be selected.
				The factory default value is 180.
			</Help>
		</Value>
	</CommandClass>
<CommandClass id="67" name="COMMAND_CLASS_THERMOSTAT_SETPOINT" version="1" request_flags="4" create_vars="true" base="0">
		<Instance index="1"/>
		<Value type="decimal" genre="user" instance="1" index="1" label="Heat" units="C" read_only="false" write_only="false" min="0" max="0" value="20"/>
		<Value type="decimal" genre="user" instance="1" index="8" label="Dry Air" units="C" read_only="false" write_only="false" min="0" max="0" value="20"/>
		<Value type="decimal" genre="user" instance="1" index="11" label="Heat Econ" units="C" read_only="false" write_only="false" min="0" max="0" value="20"/>
		<Value type="decimal" genre="user" instance="1" index="13" label="Away" units="C" read_only="false" write_only="false" min="0" max="0" value="20"/>
		<Value type="decimal" genre="user" instance="1" index="10" label="Auto Changeover" units="C" read_only="false" write_only="false" min="0" max="0" value="20"/>
	</CommandClass>
	<CommandClass id="64">
    <Instance index="1"/>
    <Value genre="user" index="0" instance="1" label="Mode" max="0" min="0" read_only="false" size="1" type="list" units="" value="0" write_only="false">
      <Item label="Off" value="0"/>
      <Item label="Heat" value="1"/>
      <Item label="Dry Air" value="8"/>
      <Item label="Auto Changeover" value="10"/>
      <Item label="Heat Econ" value="11"/>
      <Item label="Away" value="13"/>
    </Value>
    <SupportedModes>
      <Mode index="0" label="Off"/>
      <Mode index="1" label="Heat"/>
      <Mode index="8" label="Dry Air"/>
      <Mode index="10" label="Auto Changeover"/>
      <Mode index="11" label="Heat Econ"/>
      <Mode index="13" label="Away"/>
    </SupportedModes>
	</CommandClass>
<CommandClass id="133">
        <Associations num_groups="2">
            <Group index="1" max_associations="1" label="LifeLine"/>
            <Group index="2" max_associations="5" label="Relay Basic Set"/>
            <Group index="3" max_associations="5" label="S1 Basic Set"/>
            <Group index="4" max_associations="5" label="Temperature Sensor"/>
        </Associations>
    </CommandClass>
</Product>

